Finding Aid for the W.W. Robinson papers, ca. 1843-1972
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings: unpublished revisions.
  - Docket nos. 31, 37, 80 80 -D, 347 before the Indian Claims Commission. Petition for award of attorney's fees. Part four., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Docket nos. 31, 37, 80 80 - D, 347 before the Indian Claims Commission. Petition for award of attorney's fees. Part five., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Docket nos. 31, 37, 80 80 - D, 347 before the Indian Claims Commission. Petition for award of attorney's fees. Part six., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Docket nos. 31, 37, 80 80 - D, 347 before the Indian Claims Commission. Petition for award of attorney's fees. Part seven., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Docket nos. 31, 37, 80 80 - D, 347 before the Indian Claims Commission. Petition for award of attorney's fees. Part eight., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Docket nos. 31, 37, 80 80 - D, 347 before the Indian Claims Commission. Petition for award of attorney's fees. Part nine., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Comments on various chapters., No date; 16 leaves. Holograph. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    Land in California - Manuscript material.
- Biographical.
  - WWR family tree.
    - .
      - Rolled chart. (Box 133)
- California.
  - Southern California.
    - Flood lands.
      - Historical Society of Southern California, publication, v. 1 1890 p. 33-39..
        - ., 1890 (Box 129, Folder 19)
          Exceptional years, a History of California floods and drought by J. M. Guinn. Memo from Milton Anderson to WWR
      - Transcript.
        - ., June 1, 1937 (Box 129, Folder 25)
          Los Angeles County Flood Control District vs Bonnie Beach Ryan (no. 402656)
    - Pueblo of Los Angeles.
      - Jurisdiction.
        - ., 1833 (Box 129, Folder 18)
          Carbon typescript copy of no. 61. Proceedings in relation to the place named Rincon de San Pascual solicted by Don Juan Mariner, no. 97
    - Tide lands.
      - ., 1937 (Box 129, Folder 3)
        Harbor Lands Formed by Artificial Accretion
      - Addidavits.
        - ., July 1, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 32)
          Oil spill
      - Application, Oil and Gas Leases.
        - ., 1920 (Box 129, Folder 24)
          Copy. Serial Numbers 052902 to 052929
      - Applications for Federal Oil and Gas Leases Along the California Shoreline.
        - ., March 10, 1939 (Box 129, Folder 21)
          Pamphlets of maps of southern California
      - Bulletin New York State Title Association.
        - ., March 15, 1947 (Box 129, Folder 29)
          California Tidelands # 96
      - California's Offshore Oil.
        - ., 1953 (Box 129, Folder 26)
          Questions and Answers. This information issued by the Western Oil and Gas Association
      - City of Newport Beach.
        - ., n.d. (Box 129, Folder 10)
          Sarah Anne Newcomb, respondent, v. City of Newport Beach. Brief of decisions.
      - clippings.
        - ., 1950 (Box 129, Folder 4)
          Oil Operation in Tidelands Faces Halt
      - Correspondence.
        - ., Nov. 1948 (Box 129, Folder 31)
          Letters to and from Mr. H. R. Noble to WWR
      - Federal Legislative Committee of the American Title Association.
        - ., Feb. 1948 (Box 129, Folder 30)
          Tidelands Legislation, no. 264
      - General.
        - ., Aug. 1941 (Box 129, Folder 14)
          Carbon copy of Letter, M. J. Rankin to H. E. Allport
      - Legislature of California for the Sale and Conveyance of the Tide lands.
        - ., Feb. 12, 1901 (Box 129, Folder 7)
          Notes
      - letter.
        - ., Dec. 2, 1938 (Box 129, Folder 6)
          Albert Schuck to Mr. W. E. Ramsey
      - Long Beach.
        - ., April 28, 1925 (Box 129, Folder 9)
          Copy of Chapter 102, an act granting certain tidelands and submerged lands.. Approved by Governor
        - ., n.d. (Box 129, Folder 12)
          Newspaper clipping. Map showing changes of tide lands.
      - Malibu.
        - ., Sep.19, 1928 (Box 129, Folder 11)
          Motion for rehearing, Ada Monika Williams. Carbon copy.
      - notes.
        - ., n.d. (Box 129, Folder 2)
          Office Information no. 1506 for Santa Monica
        - ., n.d. (Box 129, Folder 5)
          Legislature Grants of Tidelands 1925
      - Ranchos Los Alamitos and Bay.
        - ., Oct. 2, 1941 (Box 129, Folder 8)
          Memo from Earl E. Johnson
      - Santa Monica.
        - ., Jan. 1942 (Box 129, Folder 13)
          Correspondence and memos
      - Saturday Evening Post.
        - ., May 4, 1946 (Box 129, Folder 15)
          Magazine clipping. Annexing of submerged lands.
      - Senate and House Resolution on attacks titles to state lands.
        - ., March 10, 1939 (Box 129, Folder 20)
          The Attack on States' Rights to Submerged Lands
      - State's owership of tide lands.
        - ., Dec. 1941 (Box 129, Folder 16)
          Office information no. 10768. Dale Vaughn. Typescript copies of U. S. Supreme Court reports.
      - Supreme Court.
        - ., 1947 (Box 129, Folder 27)
          Supreme Court of U. S. October Term 1947. State ownership of coastal lands
      - The New York Times.
        - ., Dec. 24, 1936 (Box 129, Folder 23)
          Asks Suit to Break California's Hold on Tidal Oil Land
      - The Story Behind the Tidelands Fight, prepared by the State of California, Robert W. Kenny, Attorney General.
        - ., Feb. 5-7, 1946 (Box 129, Folder 22)
          Booklet
      - Tide lands and petroleum rights.
        - ., 1937 (Box 129, Folder 17)
          Carbon typescript copy of Senate report no. 1234.
      - What is this Tidelands Question?.
        - ., ca. 1950's (Box 129, Folder 28)
          Pamphlet
    - Tidelands / Oil.
      - ., 1976 (Box 129, Folder 1)
        Black Gold Harbor by Malcolm Epley
- Drawing.
  - Drawing.
    - Drawing.
      - Miscellaneous landscape design.
        - . (Box 133)
          Rolled drawing
- Map.
  - Map.
    - Map.
      - Map.
        - Hand drawn map of downtown Los Angeles from Olvera Street along Los Angeles to 1st. (Box 133)
          Rolled map
  - Rolled map.
    - .
      - Map of Northern Portion of Los Angeles County., 1923 (Box 133)
        Rolled map show steam railroads, street roads, paved highways, good dirt roads trails, county lines, school district boundaries, forest reserves boundaries, ranchos boundaries and power transmission lines
- Oversize material, includes all groups.
  - Biographical.
    - Education.
      - Photographs.
        - High school or junior high school graduation., No date (Box 104, Folder 1)
          Mounted on board
    - Hicks Bibliography.
      - Photographs.
        - "Close cropped photograph of WWR." Cf. Hicks., No date / various dates (Box 104, Folder 3)
          2 prints, cropped differently
    - IBR and WWR.
      - Photographs.
        - Wedding portrait., No date (Box 104, Folder 2)
          In folder with signature [illegible] Williams
    - UC Berkeley.
      - Graduation.
        - Diploma., 1916 May 15 (Box 104, Folder 4)
          Signed by Benjamin Ide wheeler, Harry R. Hartfield (?), and Governor Hiram W. Johnson
    - WW I.
      - No subsubseries.
        - "Retreat" Ord, Supply School, Camp Hancock Ga., 1918 (Box 117, Folder 1)
          Large panorama photograph in case. Housed in URL. Spencer Wyckof, Detroit MI
  - Biographical - Organizations, Civic.
    - California Bicentennial Celbration Commission.
      - Membership material.
        - Certificate of appointment., 1967 Aug 30 (Box 104, Folder 11)
          Signed by Governor Ronald Regan and the Secretary of State
    - City of Los Angeles.
      - Outreach material.
        - Commendation., 1970 Nov (Box 104, Folder 10)
          Signed by Mayor Sam Yorty
    - Cultural Heritage Board.
      - Membership material.
        - Certificates of appointment., 1964 - 1970 (Box 104, Folder 7)
          No certificate for 1967. Most in blue folders
        - Commendation., 1970? (Box 104, Folder 9)
          Signed by Eddy S. Felman, president and Kenneth Ross, director, Dept of Municipal Arts
  - Biographical - Organizations, Historical.
    - California Historical Society.
      - Membership material.
        - Award of Merit., 1960 Jan 21 (Box 104, Folder 6)
          Signed by George L. Harding, Donald C. Biggs, and Warren R. Howell
        - Certificate electing WWR a Fellow., 1961 Jan 19 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Biographical - Organizations, Social.
    - E Clampus Vitus.
      - Membership material.
        - Certificate of membership., 1937 Oct 16 (Box 104, Folder 5)
          Signed by Lindley Bynum, J Gregg Layne, Don Rogerio Felipe Dalton
  - I. Books and Pamphlets.
    - Catalina.
      - Publication material.
        - Plate for illustration., No date / various dates (Box 103, Folder 1)
          Labels in IBR's hand
    - Maps of Los Angeles.
      - Research / publication material.
        - Los Angeles City map no.1., 1849 (Box 118, Folder 1)
          Printed copy, photograph negative print, photostat
        - Los Angeles City, Pasadena, etc., 1877 (Box 118, Folder 2)
          Photograph print, geological survey map
        - Los Angeles City abstract., 1857 (Box 118, Folder 3)
          Photostat copies, p. 31 - 34
        - Map of Zanja Madre, Los Angeles., 1888 (Box 118, Folder 4)
          Photostat
        - Maps of La Placita Olvera., 1870's (Box 118, Folder 5)
        - Map of Los Angeles (Zanja System)., 1876 (Box 118, Folder 6)
        - Map of San Bernardino Meridian, Township no. 1., 1873 (Box 118, Folder 7)
        - Plat of the Place called Cuati., 1858 (Box 118, Folder 8)
        - Plat of the Ex Mission of San Fernando., 1858 (Box 118, Folder 9)
        - Map of Rancho Rodeo de las Aguas., 1869 (Box 118, Folder 10)
        - Various maps, plats and sections of Los Angeles., 1860's - 1870's (Box 118, Folder 11)
        - Map of Los Angeles County, Abel Stearns' Ranchos., 1873 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Ranchos, Los Angeles.
    - Paso de Bartolo Viejo.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceeding on Rancho Paso de Bartolo Viejo., No date / various dates (Box 99, Folder 2)
          Unbound
  - Ranchos, Los Angeles County.
    - Agua de la Centinela.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Aguage Del Centinela., 1937 April 6 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Ex-Mission San Fernando.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on San Fernando Mission., 1937 Sept 8 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - La Ballona.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho La Ballona., 1938 Aug 23 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Los Feliz.
      - Copy.
        - Index of grantees, Rancho Los Feliz., No date / various dates (Box 98, Folder 4)
          Magenta cover
    - Los Palos Verdes.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Los Palos Verdes., 1929 Mar 22 (Box 98, Folder 5)
          5 pcs. Includes 4 maps
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Palos Verdes., 1929 Apr 3 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Rincon de Los Bueyes.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Rincon de Los Bueyes., 1938 Oct 8 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - San Antonio.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho San Antonio., 1937 Sept 22 (Box 100, Folder 2)
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho San Antonio., 1940 Nov 2 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - San Jose.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho San Jose., 1936 July 17 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - San Jose de Buenos Ayres.
      - Copy.
        - San Jose de Buenos Ayres., 1937 Sept 8 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - San Pascual.
      - Copy.
        - Patent to Manuel Garfias for Rancho San Pascual., 1863 Apr 3 (Box 100, Folder 6)
          9 leaves
    - San Pedro.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho San Pedro., 1936 Jun 3 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Santa Catalina.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings of Santa Catalina Island., 1940 Nov 2 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Sausal Redondo.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Sausal Redondo., 1937 April 6 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Tujunga.
      - Copy.
        - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Tujunga., 1949 Mar 1 (Box 101, Folder 2)
          Letter from U.S. District Court
  - Ranchos, Los Angeles County?.
    - [Check].
      - [Copy / copies].
        - [check]., No date / various dates (Box 102, Folder 1)
          Some copies (photostats) from the Bancroft, other not identified
  - Ranchos, Orange County.
    - General.
      - Copy.
        - Rancho book, Orange County., No date / various dates (Box 101, Folder 4)
          Black cover
  - Research Material.
    - A Map of Exploration in the Spanish Southwest, 1528 - 1793.
      - Publication.
        - [Los Angeles, CA] :: Automobile Club of Southern California., [1932] (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - A Map of Marked Historical Sites of California.
      - Publication.
        - [Los Angeles CA] Automobile Club of Southern California., c. 1952 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Bench and Bar of Los Angeles 1914.
      - [Copy].
        - Photograph (printed)., 1914 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Bird's eye view of San Diego, California.
      - Research/ publication.
        - From the North-East, Looking South-West., 1876 (Box 119, Folder 5)
          1 map
    - California: A Map of History.
      - Publication.
        - Flat map copyright by G.T. Dicus, artist Fred Eddy., 1950? (Box 112, Folder 2)
          Damaged, brittle. Dedicated to my good friend E.W. Biscailu and all Californians, native and adopted. Sigend: To my friend W.W. Robinson [indecipherable]
    - County Maps, Counties other than Los Angeles.
      - Publications.
        - No title., No dates / various dates (Box 113, Folder 1)
          Ventura, etc
    - General.
      - Various.
        - Fowler, D.J. Outline of the history of the telephone in the United States., No date / various dates (Box 105, Folder 1)
          In cloth boards, stamped Personal File D.J. Fowler. Also: Letter from Ann Walker to Fowler, 1928 Jan 16
        - Los Angeles research material., 1950s (late) - 1960s (Box 109, Folder 1)
          Clippings from and issues of national magazines with articles about Los Angeles: Holiday, etc
    - Geographical Survey.
      - Publication.
        - Southern California no. 1., 1948 (Box 114, Folder 1)
          Ed. Of 1901 reprinted 1948
    - Judges of the Superior Court, Los Angeles County, CAL.
      - Photographs (large pritned).
        - Portraits by Steckel., 1914 Jun (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Map of Fort Miller, Frenso County.
      - Research/ publication.
        - Drawn b C. F. Otto Skobel., ca. 1864 (Box 119, Folder 6)
          3 photostat copies of sketches
    - Map of Los Angeles County.
      - Publication.
        - No title., No date (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Map of Los Angeles County (Southern Portion).
      - Publication.
        - No title., 1913 (Box 114, Folder 6)
          Mounted on linen, one fold remaining
    - Map of San Juan Capistrano.
      - Research/ publication.
        - Map of Historic Adobes., 1935 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Map of Santa Barbara County.
      - Research/ publication.
        - Ranchos of Santa Barbara County., n.d. (Box 119, Folder 3)
          2 maps
    - Map of the City of Los Angeles.
      - Publication.
        - No publisher given, modern copy in color, seemingly different from Dawson's reprint in MGI., No date on copy (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Map of the County of Los Angeles George Hansen.
      - Publication.
        - No title., 1866 (copy) (Box 114, Folder 3)
          Blue line copy
    - Map of the County of Los Angeles Wildy and Stahlberg.
      - Publication.
        - No title., 1877 (original) (Box 114, Folder 3)
          Blue line copies
    - Map of Ventura County.
      - Research / publication material.
        - Ranchos of Ventura County., 1951 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Maps of California.
      - Research/ publication.
        - California., n.d. (Box 119, Folder 8)
          3 maps
    - Maps of Riverside County and San Bernardion.
      - Research / publication material.
        - Geological survey., 1938, 1932 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Mission San Fernando [Chronology and Map].
      - Publication.
        - No title., No date, seemingly 1940s - 1950s (Box 112, Folder 6)
          On verso, The California missions and Mission San Fernando [further history and chronologies]
    - Outdoor Play Places of California.
      - Publication.
        - [Los Angeles CA] Westings., 1954 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Rancho Boca de Santa Monica.
      - [Copy].
        - No title., 1883 Jun (Box 115, Folder 3)
          Photostats
    - Rancho la Puente.
      - [Copy].
        - No title., 1914 copied 1961 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Rancho Rincon de los Bueyes o la Cienega.
      - Copy.
        - No title., 1898 May (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Rancho San Vicente y Santa Monica.
      - [Copy].
        - No title., 1899 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Rand McNally Map of Los Angeles County.
      - Publication.
        - Chicago IL?., 1930? (Box 114, Folder 7)
          Cf. map in MGI
    - various map of counties, ranchos and mission adobes.
      - Research/ publication.
        - Yolo, San Mateo, Santa Cruz, San Luis Obispo, Somona, Monterey and San Francisco., ca. 1860's - 1936's (Box 119, Folder 7)
          8 maps
  - Research Material?.
    - General.
      - Indenture [document].
        - Harry Lancaster, Cambridge to Henry Carter, London., 1749 (Box 111, Folder 1)
          [Folders in map drawers 111 - 119]
        - Francis Ellis, Clifford, County of York to William Mountain, Thorp Arch, City of York., 1806 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - V. Articles.
    - A College Graduate in Search of a Job.
      - Publication material.
        - Clipping from: The Los Angeles Times., 1917 Nov 11 (Box 120, Folder 1)
          p. 14 - 15 and 23
    - The Laguna Art Colony.
      - Publication material.
        - Clipping from: California Southland, v.6 (1924 Jul). (Box 120, Folder 2)
          p. 10. 2 cop
  - VI. Fiction.
    - Absolutely Hygienic.
      - Publication material.
        - Clipping from: The Los Angeles Times Illustrated Weekly., 1915 Sep 18 (Saturday) (Box 120, Folder 3)
          p. 9
  - Writings - Unpublished.
    - The Land and the People.
      - Research / publication material.
        - T.I.T. scrapbook., 1890s (late) (Box 106, Folder 1)
          WWR's note on contents with box. Early forms and publications, several 1896 - 1897
        - Certificate of Honor from the Southern California Chapter of the American institute of Architects., 1930 Feb (Box 106, Folder 2)
          For the building 433 South Spring. Signed by H.C. Chambers, president, and by the secretary
        - T.I.T. scrapbooks., 1890s (late) - 1900s (early) (Box 107, Folder 1)
          WWR's note on contents with box. Some items (photographs) 1895, policy forms, notices, etc., ca. 1895 - 1901
        - T.I.T. scrapbook., 1930s (Box 108, Folder 1)
          Clippings about services and personnel, some with photographs
        - T.I.T. scrapbook: Union Trust and Title Company historical material., 1900s (early) (Box 108, Folder 2)
          Newspaper clippings, copies of correspondence, etc
        - T.I.T. memorabilia and photographs., No date / various dates (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - X. Miscellaneous? (Not in Hicks).
    - The Old Spanish and Mexican Ranchos of Orange County.
      - Publication.
        - Folded map., No date (Box 112, Folder 1)
          2 cop. 1 damaged in lower left corner, the other complete but with bad fold damage and some foxing
- Research / manuscript material - by other writers.
  - Manuscript by Others.
    - [William A. Holabird Biography].
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., ca. 1915? (Box 128, Folder 22)
          3 leaves with one note
    - I Build a R.R.; By Ervin N. Widney (?).
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., No date (Box 128, Folder 21)
          21 leaves. Typescript (carbon). With note: Touring topics
    - Some Reminiscences of Death Valley; by H.P. Gower.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Letter from James D. Hart to WWR enclosing manuscript., 1968 Mar 28 (Box 128, Folder 18)
        - Copy., 1960 (Box 128, Folder 19)
          1 preliminary leaf, 85 leaves. Typescript (photocopy)
    - The First Census of the Los Angeles District; by J. Gregg Layne.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., 1930s? (Box 128, Folder 20)
          16 leaves total. Typescript (carbon)
    - The Literary Evolution of the Wild West in Germany.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., No date (Box 128, Folder 17)
          ca. 15 leaves. Typescript (Thermofax?)
  - Manuscripts by Others.
    - [County Courthouses]; by G. Arthur Waldron.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., 1958 Sep (Box 127, Folder 8)
          8 leaves total. Typescript (carbon). Full title: Historical notes pertaining to the development of county courthouse (with references). Incorp. WWR's Hall of Records
    - [Los Angeles County Courthouse]; by G. Arthur Waldron.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Letters to WWR, enclosing the copy for review, etc., 1958 Nov 13, 1959 May 13 (Box 127, Folder 2)
        - [Copy]., 1959 (Box 127, Folder 3)
          13 leaves. Typescript (carbon). Full title: Where and when was the first Los Angeles County Courthouse established?
    - [Memoir]; by Arthur Millier.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., No date (Box 128, Folder 25)
          14, 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon). WWR: "submitted by me and Jake to Book Club of California -not followed up"
    - An Auto Trip from Los Angeles.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., No date (Box 128, Folder 24)
          9 leaves (last blank). Holograph on lined paper
    - Campo de Cahuenga; by Micheale Kemp.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., No date (Box 128, Folder 30)
          [ii], 22, [2] leaves. Typescript (carbon)
      - Research / manuscript material.
        - Correspondence with WWR., 1955 - 1956, no date (Box 128, Folder 29)
    - Edward W. Moses Poems.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Letters from Ruth Moses, and the attorneys for EM., 1962 Oct (Box 128, Folder 12)
        - Copies of poems., 1930s -. ca (Box 128, Folder 13)
          75 leaves. Various formats, including tear sheets, rev. WWR had been named literary executor, perhaps without being consulted
    - Eulalia Perez Manuscript.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., 1957 (translation) (Box 128, Folder 4)
          5 preliminary leaves, 32 leaves. Typescript. Photograph is a copy from the Bancroft
      - Publication material.
        - Letters from George Hammand., 1957 Nov - Dec (Box 128, Folder 2)
        - Supporting documents, including portrait., Various dates (Box 128, Folder 3)
          Photograph is a copy from the Bancroft
    - Letters of Butler Ives 1863 to 1869; copied by Richard J. Berry.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Copy., 1952 (Box 128, Folder 26)
          [ii], 7 leaves. Typescript (carbon) in binder
    - Little Known Los Angeles; by Jehiel Shotwell Davis.
      - Manuscript material.
        - Letter enclosing copy., 1968 Apr 14 (Box 128, Folder 5)
        - Copy., 1966 (typing). ca (Box 128, Folder 6)
          90 leaves. Various processes, including typescript
    - Los Angeles County Courthouse History / Histories.
      - Research material.
        - Hall of records; by W. W. Robinson., No date (Box 127, Folder 6)
          2 leaves total. Typescript (carbon). Unknown for what specific work
        - List of minutes, Court of Sessions., 1960 (Box 127, Folder 7)
          Photocopy. Sent to Waldron